Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Individuals PE.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- W, 1902-2005; 3.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Weiss, H., 1926 (Box 32)
  - Weiss, Max, 1947 (Box 32)
  - Weiss, Murry, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Weiss, Myra Tanner, 1997 (Box 32)
  - Weiss, Theodore, 1966 (Box 32)
  - Weisz, Morris, 1914-, 1948 (Box 32)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1979 (Box 32)
  - Wells, H.G. (Herbert George), 1866-1946, 1907 (Box 32)
  - Wells, Lester Grosvenor, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Wells, Wesley Robert, undated (Box 32)
  - Welsh, Ed, undated (Box 32)
  - Wertheimer, Barbara M., 1974 (Box 32)
  - Wertheimer, Valentin Jacob Thomas, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Wesker, Arnold, undated (Box 32)
  - Wesley, Thomas J., 1959 (Box 32)
  - West, Jim, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Westin, Alan F., 1953 (Box 32)
  - Wheeler, Susan, undated (Box 32)
  - Whitaker, John T., 1941 (Box 32)
  - White, Bouck, 1874-1951, 1913 (Box 32)
  - White, David McKelvy, 1901-, 1971 (Box 32)
  - White, John Z., 1908 (Box 32)
  - White, William Lindsay, 1900-1973, 1945 (Box 32)
  - Whitman, Walt, 1819-1892, undated (Box 32)
  - Whitney, Anita, 1867-1955, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Whitney, Caroline, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Whitney, R. M., undated (Box 32)
  - Whyte, Frederick, 1930 (Box 32)
  - Widener, Alice, undated (Box 32)
  - Wieck, David, undated (Box 32)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1928-, 1967 (Box 32)
  - Wilde, Oscar, undated (Box 32)
  - Wiley, George Alvin, 1964 (Box 32)
  - Wilkerson, Doxey Alphonso, 1905-, 1941 (Box 32)
  - Wilkes, John, 1725-1797, undated (Box 32)
  - Wilkins, Roy, 1901-1981, 1951 (Box 32)
  - Willard, Frances E. (Frances Elizabeth), 1839-1898, undated (Box 32)
  - Willard, Marcel, undated (Box 32)
  - William, Maurice, 1937 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Albert Rhys, 1919 (Box 32)
  - Williams, C. Dickerman, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Claude, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Jesse Lynch, 1871-1929, 1921 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Robert F., 1996 (Box 32)
  - Williams, Robert H., undated (Box 32)
  - Williams, T. Russell, undated (Box 32)
  - Williams, William Appleman, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Williamson, John, 1941 (Box 32)
  - Willis, Ellen, 1969 (Box 32)
  - Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944 I, 1940 (Box 32)
  - Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944 II, 1940 (Box 32)
  - Wilshire, Gaylord, 1861-1927, 1902 (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Dagmar, 1962 (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1962 (Box 32)
  - Wilson, H. H., 1963 (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Harold, 1963 (Box 32)
  - Wilson, J. Stitt, 1904, 1915 (Box 32, Box Shared Tamiment 006, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, Walter, 1903-, undated (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924, 1917 (Box 32)
  - Winchell, Walter, 1897-1972, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Winchevsky, Morris, b. 1856, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Wing, Simon, 1912 (Box 32)
  - Winitsky, Harry M., 1923 (Box 32)
  - Winship, Amy D., 1919 (Box 32)
  - Winston, Henry, 1911-1986, 1941- (Box 32)
  - Winter, Carl, 1946 (Box 32)
  - Winter, Ella, 1898-1980, 1963 (Box 32)
  - Wise, James Waterman, 1901-, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Wise, Stephen S., 1949 (Box 33)
  - Wishengrad, Morton, 1913-1963, 1961 (Box 33)
  - Wisotsky, Isidore, 1958 (Box 33)
  - Witte, Edwin E. (Edwin Emil), 1887-1960, 1947 (Box 33)
  - Wittenberg, Ruth, 1990 (Box 33)
  - Wittfogel, Karl August, 1896-1988, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Wofford, Harris, 1961 (Box 33)
  - Wofsy, Leon, undated (Box 33)
  - Wohlforth, Tim, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Wolf, Benjamin H., b. 1909, undated (Box 33)
  - Wolfe, Bertram David, 1896-1977, 1945 (Box 33)
  - Wolfe, Ella Goldberg, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Wolfe, Frank E., undated (Box 33)
  - Wolfe, James E., 1994 (Box 33)
  - Wolfgang, Myra, 1914-1976, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Wolfson, Theresa, 1897-, 1938 (Box 33)
  - Wolin, Ron, 1990 (Box 33)
  - Woll, Matthew, 1926 (Box 33)
  - Wolman, Leo, 1890-1961, 1916 (Box 33)
  - Wolsey, Louis, 1877-1953, 1928 (Box 33)
  - Woltman, Frederick, 1943 (Box 33)
  - Wood, Eugene, 1906 (Box 33)
  - Wood, Judy, undated (Box 33)
  - Wood, Myrna, undated (Box 33)
  - Woodcock, Leonard, undated (Box 33)
  - Woodhull, Victoria C. (Victoria Claflin), 1838-1927, 1893 (Box 33)
  - Woods, Dessie, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Woodsworth, J. S. (James Shaver), 1874-1942, undated (Box 33)
  - Woodward, Isaac, 1946 (Box 33)
  - Woolis, Bernie (Box 33)
  - Wordsworth, William, undated (Box 33)
  - Work, John M. (John McClelland), 1869-1961 (Box 33)
  - Worthy, William, 1921-, 1957-1962 (Box 33)
  - Wortis, Rose, 1943 (Box 33)
  - Woytinsky, Wladimir S., 1885-1960, undated (Box 33)
  - Wright, Carroll Davidson, 1911 (Box 33)
  - Wright, Fred, 1964, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Wright, Richard, 1944 (Box 33)
  - Wurmbrand, Richard, 1976 (Box 33)
- Y, 1902-2008; 1 Linear Feet in 1 record carton
  - Yablonski, Joseph A., 1910-1969, undated (Box 33)
  - Yarmolinsky, Avrahm, 1955 (Box 33)
  - Yaroslavsky, Emilian, undated (Box 33)
  - Yelensky, Boris, 1949 (Box 33)
  - Yemelyanov, V. S., undated (Box 33)
  - Yergan, Max, undated (Box 33)
  - Yerxa, Fendall, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny Aleksandrovich, 1933-, 1961 (Box 33)
  - Yoder, Dale, 1901-, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Yoneda, Karl G., 1906-, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Young, Art, 1866-1943, 1902 (Box 33)
  - Young, Juanita, 2008 (Box 33)
  - Yudin, P. F., undated (Box 33)
  - Yurick, Sol, 1981 (Box 33)
- Z, 1920-1985; 1.25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 oversize shared box
  - Zalowitz, Nathaniel, undated (Box 33)
  - Zeidler, Frank, undated (Box 33)
  - Zeluck, Steven, 1952-, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Zenger, John Peter, undated (Box 33)
  - Zetkin, Klara, 1857-1933, undated (Box 33)
  - Zilsel, Edgar, 1891-1944, 1941 (Box 33)
  - Zinke, William K., 1978 (Box 33)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1922-, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 14)
  - Zinoviev, Grigorii I, 1920- (Box 33)
  - Zinoviev, Grigorii II, 1920- (Box 33)
  - Zuk, Mary, undated (Box 33)
  - Zukerman, William, 1885-1961 (Box 33)